♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Say, you fellas know
if Jerome serves dessert here?
I got a real hankering
for pudding.
That's so weird.
I was just thinking about
pudding on the way over here.
Okay, well,
you two are clearly in love,
but I could also go
for some pudding.
Why we all got pudding
on the brain?
It's got to be
that new billboard
advertising pudding
on the highway.
We all drove past it
on the way here.
Huh.
Well, that's no surprise.
Everyone in my house
can get very excited
by a good ad campaign.
Lois! Lois, it's back!
I heard, Peter!
I heard!
Kids, kids, it's happening!
Get your coats!
This is what we practiced for!
I love you, Dad!
I love you, too, sweetheart!
None of the past matters!
Oh, yeah, I seen
that pudding billboard.
It's that one that says
"CBS Outdoor Advertising" on it.
Yeah, but right above that is,
like, a big guy eating pudding.
I don't remember none of that.
I just remember
"CBS Outdoor Advertising"
on the bottom and three pigeons
sitting on top.
You're bad at looking
at billboards.
Hey, we should go
check it out right now.
Ordinarily I'd say no, but
that adult kickball league
is coming in for drinks,
so let's get out of here.
Guys, check it out.
I've got flip-up shades
on my flip-up shades.
Dude, you are the worst.
Hey, we're all the worst.
That's real
pudding in there.
What? No, it isn't.
They wouldn't put real pudding
on a billboard, Peter.
Do you have any idea how
crippled you sound right now?
Peter, it's not real pudding.
God, sometimes I just want
to shake some sense into you.
Big talk for a guy
who looks like a dad
at a Dave Matthews'
concert.
Everybody hates how
you dress, right, Joe?
Sorry, I stay out
of fashion debates.
I've been burned
one too many times.
Hey, guys,
notice anything different?
Yeah, Minetti's got
a hot new look.
The whole thing,
it just works.
Minetti.
Look, there's only one
way to settle this.
I am climbing that billboard
to prove it's real pudding.
Moisturizer?
Sure.
Okay.
We getting on
into the chappy season.
Peter, be careful
up there!
Is this being
careful enough, Joe?
Okay. All right.
Peter, are you okay?!
All right, there's no pudding,
but there is a kid up here.
Don't hold him like that.
Oh, my God!
Peter, that's the lost
Nicholson kid!
He's been missing for a week!
Oh, yeah.
They arrested a
custodian 'cause of you.
Peter, stay put.
I'll call this in,
and we'll get a crew
out here to help you both down.
All right,
but can you hurry it up?
I got band practice later.
I love playing the maracas.
They're so fun.
I wonder what's in them.
Sand or rice probably.
Maybe it's little shells.
Oh, no, what if it's bones?
No, no, bones are too big.
But baby bones aren't.
No, no, no, nobody would kill
a bunch of babies for maracas.
How would you kill
all those babies anyway?
I'd probably put them in a tub.
You could kill, like,
eight at a time that way.
Plus, it softens them up,
so you can get
the bones right out.
Joe just had a baby.
And I got a baby at home.
I got a tub.
Peter, you seem off today.
Are you thinking
about killing infants again?
No.
Now you got to kill them, too.
Mikey, you're safe!
Thank you so much
for finding my boy.
Thank you for
finding her boy.
I'm the stepfather.
Peter Griffin,
in recognition of your heroism
in helping to rescue
little Mikey Nicholson,
I'd like to present you
with this key to the city.
Now don't forget to water
the plants every other day
and change the cat's litter.
I'll see you in two weeks.
No parties.
Thank you, Mayor West.
You know, some of you
out there are calling me a hero.
Others are calling me a hoagie.
Those of you from Connecticut
are calling me a grinder.
I guess what
I'm trying to say is
I'm not just pieces of meat
between pieces of bread.
I am a man
who unintentionally saves kids.
Wow.
20 years on the force,
and no one's ever clapped
for me.
Except for that one
sarcastic gay guy.
Great observation.
I know you mean the opposite
of what you're saying.
Fact is, when I saved that boy,
I wasn't thinking.
I don't think. I just do.
I wanted to see if a billboard
had real pudding in it,
so I climbed up there
and came out a hero.
It's just like Gandhi
always said,
eat as much as you want
and do whatever,
and don't be afraid
to hit each other.
Way to go, Dad.
Peter, that thing you
said about not thinking
and just doing stuff,
did you mean that?
Sure I did, Joe.
I never stop to think.
That's why I've had ringworm
11 times.
I will roll in anything.
You know what, you're right.
And it's time I do
the same thing.
Hey, Chief. It's Swanson.
I quit.
Joe Swanson.
I don't know
if Ray Swanson's quitting.
You'd have to ask him.
Okay, you just called me
Ray again.
I just want to confirm that
you understand that this is Joe.
No, not "see you tomorrow."
Joe, what are you doing?
You can't quit your job.
Well, that's
the other thing, Bonnie.
You and I are done, too.
What?!
I'm leaving you.
New Joe!
Wow. I can't remember the
last time Joe shot his gun.
I know. That bullet's
been rolling around
in his junk drawer for years.
Hey, Ma, guess where I am?
Yeah, can you hear it?
Flying through the air.
I don't know what he shot at.
I guess I'll just have
to find out when I land.
No, don't put Terry on.
You-you can just tell him.
H-Hey. Hi, Terry.
Oh, God.
What?
"What?"
You know what.
I think it looks good.
You are, you are just
trying anything, aren't you?
Just searching for
an identity, man.
And you think this
is gonna be it, huh?
Oh, God, whatever.
Peter, I'm worried
about Joe.
You know, not only
did he quit his job,
he's moved out and gotten
his own apartment.
Oh, I feel terrible for
Bonnie and the kids.
Ah, they'll be fine.
They'll bounce back.
Just like Humpty Dumpty did
after his fall.
My God, it's a miracle!
You were able to put me
back together again.
Yeah, it was actually
a pretty simple procedure.
Maybe next time go straight
to a medical professional
and skip the horses
and illiterate servants.
Well, that is the last time
I drink and masturbate
on top of a high wall.
Wait, wait, Quagmire, hold up.
I got a great knock.
Oh, I got to remember that.
Oh, hey, guys.
How's it going?
Hey, buddy.
How you doing?
You okay?
Everything okay?
I'm talking like this
because I'm being very careful
not to upset you,
and for some reason
this is the voice people use
to do that.
I'm great.
Come on in.
Check out the new pad.
Whoa!
You got an air hockey table?
Yep. Wanted it, got it.
That's the new Joe.
And check this out.
It's the gun
that no-leg sprinter used
to kill his girlfriend.
Oh, my God!
Eh, anyone who's kind of fast
gets a free pass from me.
What kind of person
would want to buy that?
I'll tell you who.
The kind of guy
who's always got
butterscotch candies
for his friends.
Okay, now that's pretty cool.
I got to be honest,
Joe, we came over here
because we were
worried about you,
but these candies tell
me you're doing great.
I've never been better.
I was living my life all wrong.
But not anymore.
No more thinking, just living.
Well, it seems like you made
the right choice, Joe.
I mean, I ain't seen
anyone this happy
since the invention
of the penny-farthing bicycle.
Eureka! Watch it go.
Higher than you,
faster than you,
better than you.
Everyone just stop inventing
stuff now,
'cause no one
will ever top this.
Oh, no!
Keep rakes away.
I expressly said no rakes
allowed on the street
when I am riding my
futuristic machine.
Children, this is progress!
How can you turn a blind eye
to progress?!
I expressly said "no rakes."
'Sup, ladies?
Oh, we're not ladies, you.
Hey, what's with
the suitcase?
I got a surprise.
What would you guys think
of a road trip?
Yeah!
All right, I'm in!
Awesome, road trip!
I love being super pumped
for 15 minutes
and then bored out of my mind
for eight hours.
Where we going?
Well, I was thinking
Niagara Falls.
Niagara Falls?
Ain't that just for lovers?
Nah, it's for everybody.
It's great to just stand there
and let Mother Nature spray it
all over your face.
Donna's big fat aunt is in town,
so I can definitely go.
Man, I am filling
these Gatorade bottles
as fast as I'm drinking them.
Ah, sweet! Cows!
Let's tip them over.
What? You want
to tip over some cows?
Hell yeah!
This is gonna
be so boss.
I can't wait.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever done in my life.
All right, cow.
This is what you get
for standing.
That...
was awesome.
I want to kiss that cow,
but I don't want it
to be my idea.
Hey, Peter, you should
kiss that cow.
All right, Peter,
that was fortuitous.
But play it cool.
Oh, Cleveland, I couldn't.
Okay. Quagmire,
you should kiss that cow.
Sure, why not?
Okay, they're sleeping.
We're gonna have to party
in the bathroom.
Be careful around
the really fat one.
He's kind of like my boss.
What? Who-who's there?
Joe, what the hell
are you doing?
I went to
a high school kegger party.
Made a few new friends.
This is Chrysalis,
Ichabod and Cancer.
Oh, I see
three young men
who could use the
tickle monster.
Uh, that's a bad read, Pete.
Joe, it's 3:00
in the morning.
We're trying to
get some sleep.
You guys are lame.
We're gonna go smoke
something called "croak."
God, what the hell
has gotten into Joe?
I don't know, Quagmire.
Maybe you could
ask the tickle monster!
Stop it! Here he comes!
No! Get away!
He's gonna get ya!
Look out!
Great, now I'm fully up.
Here we are, guys,
Niagara Falls.
We showed them.
We showed them all!
Showed who? What the
hell's he talking about?
I don't know.
I stopped listening to him
back at the drive-thru
when he leaned out the window
and ordered a "fur burger."
That's not funny;
that's just nasty.
Plus, there's people waiting
behind you!
Wow. You know, when
you see it up close,
it really is
incredible.
Yeah. Holy crap,
it's beautiful.
In the future, I believe
there will be water wars.
You know, Lois always dreamed
about coming here,
and now I know why.
She was even
saving money for it.
You made it, Lois.
You made it.
Didn't I tell you guys?
It's the most magnificent place
in the world.
And the greatest place
to end it all.
Good-bye, fellas.
Oh, my God, Joe killed himself!
It's so weird
that he argued
over the price
of breakfast this morning.
It makes no sense!
Damn it!
Joe?
Joe, you're alive!
Are you hurt?
I'm not sure.
Well, hang in there, Joe,
we'll get some help.
No! Just let me die!
Oh, no, can't do that, Joe.
We're friends.
We look out for each other.
I mean, you supported me
that day
I accidentally wore
Lois's jeans.
Peter, you know
you're wearing...
I know. I think
there was a mix-up.
Oh, thank you, Jazzercize.
Don't worry, Joe.
They're coming for you.
Yay! My backpack.
Hang in there, Joe.
After they get that lady's hat,
you're next.
Thank you.
It's windy up here.
Joe, what the hell
is wrong with you?
Why would you try
to kill yourself?
Why do you think? I'm worthless.
But y-you've been so happy
these last few days.
I've been manic.
Do you think Andy Dick
is happy?
I couldn't imagine, no.
Look, when I saw Peter
become a hero,
I guess it reminded me
of all the things I can't do.
I'm a cop who can't save anyone.
I'm a husband
in a legless marriage.
My whole life is a joke.
But somehow, as soon
as I decided to kill myself,
I actually felt free.
Almost giddy.
I can finally kiss
this worthless life good-bye.
Let me get
this straight.
The whole point of bringing
us to Niagara Falls
was just to
kill yourself?
I'm sorry I tricked
you guys into coming.
I just wanted to spend
my last week with my best pals.
Well, not for nothing, but
you could've taken us all
to Disney World and shot
yourself in the room.
Come on, Joe, there's plenty
of reasons to live.
Like, like, you're handsome.
You have a handsome face.
Well, he's got
a good chin.
I don't know
about handsome.
Yeah, he's not handsome,
but I will say this,
he keeps a good lawn.
Yeah, some might say the second
best lawn in the neighborhood.
Hey, wait, where's Joe?
Joe, wait!
I stink at this.
Anywhere is fine.
Guys, this is
unnecessary.
Give me my chair back.
No, we can't trust you
not to kill yourself.
Yeah, then you'd be
the tenth friend
who's killed himself
in front of me.
Is that true?
One, two, three,
four, five,
six, seven...
those two girls and...
Yeah, yeah, ten.
Look, you guys,
what we really need to do
is bring him back to Quahog
where we can get him some help.
That's a good idea.
We should just go home.
Yeah, I guess
you're right.
It's too bad we already
bought those tickets
for the Whirlpool
Aero Car.
That's $16
we're not getting back.
Yeah, what a waste of money.
It is only a ten-minute
ride, you know.
Okay, we'll do
the Whirlpool Aero Car,
and then take Joe
back to Quahog.
What about
the White Water Walk?
Okay, okay, Whirlpool Aero Car,
then White Water Walk,
then we bring Joe back.
Well, you can't do
Niagara Falls
without riding the
Maid of the Mist.
Yeah, let's do everything.
Great!
And, guys, remember,
the pool towels go home with us.
They got no way
of accounting for those.
Well, this has just been
one heck of a fun day.
Yeah. Yeah, you know,
seeing the natural beauty
of this place
is actually making me
feel much better.
Hey, you mind opening that door?
Get a little breeze in here?
Sure.
Peter, no!
I don't regret it.
The breeze is nice.
Oh, crap, I'm losing my grip!
You buy your jeans
at Wal-Mart?
No, somebody who lost theirs
at the church did.
You wear
lost-and-found jeans?
I waited the mandatory week.
Hang on, guys!
Don't worry, I'm coming!
What's that thing he's on?
It's a chair with wheels!
He's an absolute dream.
Guys, keep swallowing water.
We'll drink our way
out of this.
Guys, grab on to my legs!
Got it!
Ew. You know, this is actually
the first time
I've ever touched Joe.
Don't worry, I gotcha.
Oh, thank God, Joe.
I thought I was dead!
I even pictured
my own funeral.
♪ Grandma got run over
by a reindeer ♪
♪ Walking home from our house
Christmas Eve... ♪
I don't know, Chris.
I don't know why
he wanted this,
but we're honoring
your father's wishes.
Ah, I'm gonna miss my daddy!
Joe, that was amazing.
You saved us.
Yeah, I guess I did.
You know, I spent the whole time
trying to kill myself,
but it took seeing
you guys almost die
to realize that life
really is worth living.
See, Joe, you're
a hero, too.
And we wouldn't trade you
for any friend in the world.
I'm lucky to have you guys
in my life.
♪ We're four friends ♪
♪ Having an adventure ♪
♪ Four friends... ♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's that song?
Nothing.
I made it up.
Well, stop it.
It's terrible.
I don't think so.
It's catchy.
♪ We're four friends ♪
♪ Having an adventure ♪
♪ Four friends ♪
Ah, what the hell.
♪ Having an adventure ♪
♪ Four friends ♪
♪ At Niagara Falls. ♪
Wow, that was awesome.
Yeah, definitely.
All right, okay,
don't anyone sing anything else
until we get home.
We got to record this.
Yeah, that'll be great.
♪ I'm a Barbie girl
in a Barbie world ♪
♪ Come on, Barbie,
let's go party! ♪
Peter, damn it, no!
Wait, wait, we got to remember
the other one.
What was it, Joe?
It's gone.
Well, that was kind of a weird
trip, but I'm glad we went.
Yeah, I love
Niagara Falls.
I was the only black man
ever to go there.
The tourists were
taking pictures of me.
One of them thought
I was a bear.
Hey, guys.
Wow, Joe, you got your job back?
Sure did.
How'd you pull that off?
Ah, they always need more cops.
Turns out not many people
want to probably get shot
for $24,000 a year.
And what about Bonnie?
How you getting her back?
Well, I got a plan for that.
I hired some guys
to come to the house
on Tuesday and assault her,
and I'll come in and save her,
and she'll be so grateful,
she'll have to take me back.
Joe, today's Tuesday.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru
Well, poop.